Guide to the Judson Memorial Church Archive MSS.094
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretion 2001- Series G: Media
  - Subseries 1B: Audiocassettes - Originals
    - Cassettes - Judson Gallery - Conversation at Lil Picard's with Hendricks, Hansen, and Ortiz after Destruction in Art Symposium - 3/8/68 and 3/22/68, 1968 (Box .01.13, Media ID: 094.0261, Media ID: 094.0082)
      This tape suffers from sticky shed syndrome and presented multiple speed issues.
    - Cassettes - Judson Gallery - Ralph Ortiz - Piano Destruction Concert -- 1966-- Jean Toche -Statement -, ID: 094.0083 (Box .01.13, Media ID: 094.0083)
      This tape shows signs of sticky shed syndrome
    - Cassettes - Judson in the 1950's - A Discussion Group - 1980(?), ID: 094.0262 (Box .01.13, Media ID: 094.0262)
    - Cassettes - Judson Jubilee - A Service of Commemoration, Thanksgiving and Commitment - 5/16/76, 1976; ID: 094.0263 (Box .01.13, Media ID: 094.0263)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "About Time"- Part I & II - 4/23/70 and 4/26/70, 1970; ID: 094.0264 (Box .01.13, Media ID: 094.0264, Media ID: 094.0265)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "About Time"- Part I - 1970, cuid7035 (Box .01.13, Media ID: 094.0266, Media ID: 094.0267, Media ID: 094.0268)
      This tape was not transferred because it is a duplicate of ID: 094.0264
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "About Time"-Part II - 1970, ID: 094.0270 (Box .01.13, Media ID: 094.0270, Media ID: 094.0269)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"The Agony of Paul"Act I, Part 1, Act II-10/26/80, 1980; cuid7036 (Box .01.13, Media ID: 094.0273, Media ID: 094.0272, Media ID: 094.0271)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "The Agony of Paul" Act II - 10/26/80, 1980; ID: 094.0274 (Box .01.13, Media ID: 094.0274, Media ID: 094.0276, Media ID: 094.0275)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "The Beast: A Meditation on Beauty" -11/26/76, 1976; cuid7037 (Box .01.13, Media ID: 094.0278, Media ID: 094.0277)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "A Beautiful Day" - 6/2/66, 1966; ID: 094.0279 (Box .01.13, Media ID: 094.0279)
      This tape was not transferred due to its poor condition (sticky shed syndrome)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "A Birthday Tribute to Irving Berlin" -6/11/78, 1978; ID: 094.0280 (Box .01.13, Media ID: 094.0280)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "The Bonus Army" - Mar-76, 1976; ID: 094.0281 (Box .01.13, Media ID: 094.0281)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "Camp Meeting: 1840" - 6/5/76, 1976; ID: 094.0285 (Box .01.13, Media ID: 094.0285, Media ID: 094.0283, Media ID: 094.0284, Media ID: 094.0282)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"Camp Meeting" - 8/28/77, 1977; cuid7038 (Box .01.13, Media ID: 094.0287, Media ID: 094.0286)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "Chant A Capella" - 11/20/77, 1977; ID: 094.0288 (Box .01.13, Media ID: 094.0288)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "Christmas Rappings" - sound effect - no date, undated; ID: 094.0289 (Box .01.13, Media ID: 094.0289)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "Christmas Rappings"- 12/20/75, 1975; ID: 094.0290 (Box .01.13, Media ID: 094.0290)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "Christmas Rappings" - 12/18/76, 1976; ID: 094.0291 (Box .01.13, Media ID: 094.0291)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "Christmas Rappings"-12/21/77, 1977; ID: 094.0292 (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0292)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "Christmas Rappings"-12/16/78, 1978; ID: 094.0293 (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0293)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "Christmas Rappings"-12/21/80, 1980; ID: 094.0294 (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0294)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"Dr. Faustus Lights the Lights" - 11/17/79, 1979; ID: 094.0213 (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0213, Media ID: 094.0211, Media ID: 094.0212, Media ID: 094.0210)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "The Faggot" - Nov-73, 1973 (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0295, Media ID: 094.0296)
      This tape suffers from sticky shed syndrome, which may affect the quality of the recording. It is a duplicate of 094.0296, which could not be transferred.
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"The Faggot" & "The Song of Solomon" - no date, undated; ID: 094.0297 (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0297)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"Joan" - Act I & II - no date, undated; ID: 094.0298 (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0298, Media ID: 094.0301, Media ID: 094.0299, Media ID: 094.0300)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "The Journey of Snow White" - no date, undated (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0303, Media ID: 094.0302)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "The Journey of Snow White" - 1975, ID: 094.0304 (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0304, Media ID: 094.0305)
      This tape shows signs of sticky shed syndrome, which may affect the quality of the recording.
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "The Journey of Snow White" - Part I&II -1975, cuid7041 (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0307, Media ID: 094.0308, Media ID: 094.0309, Media ID: 094.0306)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "The Journey of Snow White" -Act I&II - 1975, ID: 094.0312 (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0312, Media ID: 094.0311, Media ID: 094.0313, Media ID: 094.0310)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "The Journey of Snow White" -Act II - 1975 (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0428, Media ID: 094.0314, Media ID: 094.0315)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"The Life of a Man" - Act I, Part 1 - Oct-72, 1972; ID: 094.0316 (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0316)
      This tape was damaged, which may affect the quality of the recording. It was spliced and rehoused by Preservation.
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"A Look at the '50's" - Apr-72, 1972; ID: 094.0320 (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0320, Media ID: 094.0317, Media ID: 094.0319, Media ID: 094.0318)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"A Manoir" by Gertrude Stein - 5/21/77, 1977; cuid7043 (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0216, Media ID: 094.0217)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"A Nosegay of Old Songs"-5/25/80, 1980; ID: 094.0321 (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0321, Media ID: 094.0322)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"In Praise of Death" - 11/18/78, 1978 (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0323, Media ID: 094.0324)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater - "Religion" - Act I, II, III - no date, undated; ID: 094.0325 (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0325, Media ID: 094.0326)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"Sacred and Profane Love"- 3/24/75, 1975 (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0327)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"San Francisco's Burning" - no date, undated; ID: 094.0328 (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0328)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"Sing Ho for a Bear" - 1/8/65, 1965; ID: 094.0330 (Box .01.14, Media ID: 094.0330, Media ID: 094.0329, Media ID: 094.0331)
      This tape suffers from sticky shed syndrome, which may affect the quality of the recording.
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"Someone's in the Kitchen with Dinah" - 8/10/79, 1979 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0332)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"Song of Songs" - 1967, ID: 094.0333 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0333, Media ID: 094.0334)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"A Spring Bouquet of Old Songs" - 5/3/76, 1976; ID: 094.0335 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0335)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"A Summer Bouquet of Old Songs" -6/18/79, 1979; ID: 094.0336 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0336)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"T.S. Eliot: MidWinter Vigil(ante) - 4/12/81, 1981; ID: 094.0337 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0337)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"Tatyana Repina" by Anton Chekov - 4/15/78, 1978; ID: 094.0338 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0338)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"The Urban Crisis" - 11/2/69, 1969; ID: 094.0340 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0340, Media ID: 094.0339)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"W.C." - Summer 1980 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0342, Media ID: 094.0341)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"Wanted" -by Daniel Epstein - Feb-72, 1972; ID: 094.0343 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0343)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"What Happened?" - 4/6/66 and 4/25/66, 1966; ID: 094.0214 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0214, Media ID: 094.0215)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"Why I Love New York" - 10/25/75, 1975 (Box .01.15, Media 094.0345, Media ID: 094.0346, Media ID: 094.0347, Media ID: 094.0344)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"Judson Songs for Howard and Lorry" -4/26/92, 1992; ID: 094.0348 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0348)
    - Cassettes - Judson Poet's Theater -"Judson Songs for the Kids" - no date, undated; ID: 094.0349 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0349)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - Al Carmines Returns - 1/8/78, 1978; ID: 094.0350 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0350)
      This tape has some static interference, which may affect the quality of the recording.
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service -Celebration of Reentry & Renewal - 11/13/77, 1977; ID: 094.0351 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0351, Media ID: 094.0352)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service -Christmas in Concert - 12/14/86, 1986 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0353)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 2/18/89, 1989; ID: 094.0354 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0354)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 4/7/91, 1991; ID: 094.0355 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0355)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 4/14/91, 1991; ID: 094.0356 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0356)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 4/21/91, 1991; ID: 094.0357 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0357)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 4/28/91, 1991; ID: 094.0358 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0358)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 5/5/91, 1991; ID: 094.0359 (Box .01.15, Media ID: 094.0359)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service -Mother's Day - 5/12/91, 1991; ID: 094.0360 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0360)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 9/8/91, 1991; ID: 094.0361 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0361)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 9/15/91, 1991; ID: 094.0362 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0362)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 9/29/91, 1991; ID: 094.0363 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0363)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 10/6/91, 1991; ID: 094.0364 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0364)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 10/12/91, 1991; ID: 094.0365 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0365)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 10/20/91, 1991; ID: 094.0366 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0366)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 10/27/91, 1991; ID: 094.0367 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0367)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 11/3/91, 1991; ID: 094.0368 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0368)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 11/24/91, 1991; ID: 094.0369 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0369)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 12/1/91, 1991; ID: 094.0370 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0370)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 12/8/91, 1991; ID: 094.0371 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0371)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service -12/5/91, 1991; ID: 094.0372 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0372)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 12/22/91, 1991; ID: 094.0373 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0373)
      This tape was not transferred because it was found to be blank.
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 12/29/91, 1991; ID: 094.0374 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0374)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 1/12/92, 1992; ID: 094.0375 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0375)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 1/26/92, 1992; ID: 094.0376 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0376)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 2/9/92, 1992; ID: 094.0377 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0377)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 2/2/92, 1992; ID: 094.0378 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0378)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 2/16/92, 1992; ID: 094.0379 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0379)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 2/23/92, 1992; ID: 094.0380 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0380)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 3/1/92, 1992; ID: 094.0381 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0381)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 3/8/92, 1992; ID: 094.0382 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0382)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 3/15/92, 1992; ID: 094.0383 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0383)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 4/5/92, 1992; ID: 094.0384 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0384)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service - 4/12/92, 1992; ID: 094.0385 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0385)
    - Cassettes - Judson Worship Service -4/19/92, ID: 094.0386 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0386)
    - Cassettes - Memorial Service -Arlene Rothlein - 12/15/76, 1976; ID: 094.0387 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0387)
    - Cassettes - Memorial Service -Don Nute - 9/11/91, 1991; ID: 094.0388 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0388)
    - Cassettes - Memorial Service -Hugh Pickett - 3/4/92, 1992; ID: 094.0389 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0389)
    - Cassettes - Memorial Service -Richard Schmiechen - 5/23/93, 1993; ID: 094.0390 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0390, Media ID: 094.0391)
    - Cassettes - Memorial Service -Robert W Spike - 10/10/66, 1966 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0392)
    - Cassettes - Moody, Howard -"A Conversation with Rev Lawrence Hosie" -2/1978, 1900; ID: 094.0394 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0394, Media ID: 094.0393)
    - Cassettes - Moody, Howard -"Celebration:20 Year at Judson Church" - 2/4/77, 1977 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0395, Media ID: 094.0396)
    - Cassettes - Moody, Howard and Lorrie - 20th Anniversary Celebration - 4/3/77, 1977; ID: 094.0398 (Box .01.16, Media ID: 094.0398, Media ID: 094.0397)
    - Cassettes - Moody, Howard - M&M Luncheon -- 1991 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0399, Media ID: 094.0400)
    - Cassettes - Moody, Howard - Retirement Party - 4/11/92, 1992; ID: 094.0402 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0402, Media ID: 094.0401)
    - Cassettes - Moody, Howard - Study Group on Judson - 5/4/89, 1989 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0403)
    - Cassettes - Ordination Service - Charles Babian - 3/29/92, 1992; ID: 094.0404 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0404)
    - Cassettes - Ordination Service -Gary Comstock - 3/12/89, 1989; ID: 094.0405 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0405)
    - Cassettes - Ordination Service-Holly Vincent Bean -5/21/89, 1989; ID: 094.0406 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0406)
    - Cassettes - Palm Sunday at Judson - 3/24/91, 1991; ID: 094.0407 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0407)
    - Cassettes - The Prostitution Project -"Church Bus" - Nov-73, 1973; ID: 094.0429 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0429)
    - Cassettes - Woody's Children/Weavers - 1980, ID: 094.0408 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0408)
    - Cassettes - Miscellaneous - "C&C at C" - Dec-69, 1969; ID: 094.0409 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0409, Media ID: 094.0410)
    - Cassettes - Miscellaneous - Entertainment/Kristin McNutt - 1980 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0411)
    - Cassettes - Miscellaneous - "One Little Child" - 1991, ID: 094.0412 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0412)
    - Cassettes - Miscellaneous -"Diane talking about Calvin, her former man" - 3/29/84, 1984; ID: 094.0413 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0413)
    - Cassettes - Miscellaneous-MLK Funeral Service-- Interview of Kert Kren-- Lunch by Lil Picard and John Hendricks -- 1968, ID: 094.0084 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0084)
      This tape shows signs of sticky shed syndrome, which may affect the audio quality
    - Cassettes - Miscellaneous - Memorial Weekend - Beer Garden at Judson -1970's (?), [1970-1979]; ID: 094.0414 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0414)
    - Cassettes - Miscellaneous- Schneeman - "Meat Joy" - Nov-64, 1964; ID: 094.0088 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0088)
    - Cassettes - Miscellaneous - Stein Tribute - 1973 and WBAI Benefit - 1974, 1905; ID: 094.0415 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0415)
    - Cassettes - Miscellaneous - "Tales of Plagues and Carnivals" -no date, undated; ID: 094.0416 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0416)
    - Cassettes - Miscellaneous - Tape from Answering Machine at Judson-12/24/87, 1987; ID: 094.0417 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0417)
      The content on this tape is barely audible.
    - Cassettes - Miscellaneous - "Tricks" - 5/18/85, 1985; ID: 094.0418 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0418)
    - Cassettes - Miscellaneous - Unmarked Cassette and Various Commercial Cassettes, undated; ID: 094.0423 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0423, Media ID: 094.0424, Media ID: 094.0421, Media ID: 094.0422, Media ID: 094.0420, Media ID: 094.0419)
  - Subseries 1C: Audiocassettes - Submasters - CLOSED
    - Construction-Deconstruction-Construction, 2007-12 (Box Shared Fales PM 1, Case 094.0093)
      Source ID
      094.0081
    - Conversation after Destruction in Art Symposium, 2007-12 (Box Shared Fales PM 1, Case 094.0097)
      094.0082 side A only
    - Conversation after Destruction in Art, 2007-12 (Box Shared Fales PM 1, Case 094.0099)
      094.0082 side B only
    - Piano Deconstruction Concert, 2007-12 (Box Shared Fales PM 1, Case 094.0102)
      094.0083
    - Lunch by Picard & Hendricks, 2007-12 (Box Shared Fales PM 1, Case 094.0105)
      094.0084
    - Items Meat Joy, undated (Box Shared Fales PM 1, Case 094.0117)
      094.0088
    - Audio submaster, undated (Box Shared Fales PM 1, Case 094.0439)
      094.0217
    - Audio submaster, undated (Box Shared Fales PM 1, Case 094.0436)
      094.0216 part 2
    - Audio submaster, undated (Box Shared Fales PM 1, Case 094.0435)
      094.0216 part 1
    - Audio submaster, undated (Box Shared Fales PM 1, Case 094.0433)
      094.0214
    - Audio submaster, undated (Box Shared Fales PM 1, Case 094.0431)
      094.0213
    - Audio submaster, undated (Box Shared Fales PM 1, Case 094.0429)
      094.0212
  - Subseries 2: Audio Reels
    Audio reels have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
    - Reels - "Carmines Playing Carmines", undated (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0425)
    - Reels -"The Bonus Army", undated; ID: 094.0426 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0426)
    - Reels -"The Bonus Army", undated; ID: 094.0427 (Box 107, Media ID: 094.0427)
  - Subseries 3: Videorecordings
    Video recordings have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
    - M&M Luncheon (ABC Biennial); Howard Moody, 6/18/1991., ID: 094.0023 (Box .01.17, Media ID: 094.0023)
      1/2" VHS videocassette. Tape length 120 minutes.
    - Judson; MLK, Jr. Celebration (Channel 4 News), 1/14/1990., ID: 094.0024 (Box .01.17, Media ID: 094.0024)
    - Yoko Ono (WCBS TV News), 1/19/1990., ID: 094.0025 (Box .01.17, Media ID: 094.0025)
    - "Too Soon to Compromise"., undated; ID: 094.0026 (Box .01.17, Media ID: 094.0026)
      1/2" S-VHS videocassette. Tape length 30 minutes.
    - Stainglass Work in Churches - N.Y. View (WABC), 4/1/1989., ID: 094.0027 (Box .01.17, Media ID: 094.0027)
      1/2" VHS videocassette. Tape length 10 minutes.
  - Subseries 5: Slides
    - Slides - Unidentified Artwork, undated (Box .01.17, Folder 30)
    - Slides - Color Transparencies, undated (Box .01.17, Folder 31)
    - Slides - Color Transparencies, undated (Box .01.17, Folder 32)
- Accretion 2009 - Series A: Arts, 1920-2000; 1960-2000
  - Subseries 1: Arts-General
    - Funding requests, Judson Poets' Theater, 1971-1975 (Box .09.01, Folder 1)
    - Funding request - "Camp Meeting", 1977 (Box .09.01, Folder 2)
    - Funding request to Con Edison, 1977 (Box .09.01, Folder 3)
    - Funding request to the Peg Satvoord Fund, 1977 (Box .09.01, Folder 4)
    - Funding request to Mobil Oil Corporation, 1977 (Box .09.01, Folder 5)
    - Funding request to Scherman Foundation, 1977 (Box .09.01, Folder 6)
    - Funding request to Ford Foundation, 1977-1978 (Box .09.01, Folder 7)
    - Funding request to Exxon Corporation, 1977-1978 (Box .09.01, Folder 8)
    - Funding request to Booth Ferris Foundation, 1996 (Box .09.01, Folder 9)
    - Fundraising in Art Community, 1990-1999 (Box .09.01, Folder 10)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - Judson Poets' Theater Symposium (Box .09.01, Folder 11)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - articles (Box .09.01, Folder 12)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - Forum on Racial Polarities in NYC (Box .09.01, Folder 13)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - La Gran Scena Opera Co. press kit (Box .09.01, Folder 14)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - theater usher orientation (Box .09.01, Folder 15)
    - Judson Centennial (1890-1990) - "Christmas Rappings" lighting plot by Earl Eidman (Box .09.01, Folder 16)
    - Movement Research, 1991-1992 (Box .09.01, Folder 17)
    - Movement Research, 1993-1994 (Box .09.01, Folder 18)
    - Movement Research, 1995-1996 (Box .09.01, Folder 19)
    - Movement Research, 1997-1998 (Box .09.01, Folder 20)
    - Arts, General - Flier for musical, circa 1920 (Box .09.01, Folder 21)
    - Arts, General - Britten...Ceremony of Carols, poster, undated (Box .09.01, Folder 22)
    - Arts, General - Religious Art, poster, undated (Box .09.01, Folder 23)
    - Arts, General - "The Church and the Frontier of the Arts" by Bernard Scott, 1960 (Box .09.01, Folder 24)
    - Arts, General - Photo: Judson Studio Players' production of Goethe's Faust directed by Chuck Dordone (?), 1960 (Box .09.01, Folder 25)
    - Arts, General - Hall of Issues - Against the Inevitable Decline of a Great Nation, 1960 (Box .09.01, Folder 26)
    - Arts, General - Hall of Issues - poster/call to artists, 1961 (Box .09.01, Folder 27)
    - Arts, General - Hall of Issues, 1961-1967 (Box .09.01, Folder 28)
    - Arts, General - Hall of Issues, posters, 1961-1962 (Box .09.01, Folder 29)
    - Arts, General - Hall of Issues, proposals, 1961-1962 (Box .09.01, Folder 30)
    - Arts, General - Hall of Issues, photos, 1961-1962 (Box .09.01, Folder 31)
    - Arts, General - Hall of Issues, related spin-offs, 1960s (Box .09.01, Folder 32)
    - Arts, General - photos, Judson Arts Workshop, 1966 (Box .09.01, Folder 33)
    - Arts, General - Judson chamber concerts, 1967-1968 (Box .09.01, Folder 34)
    - Arts, General - Judson Three Defense Fund, 1970 (Box .09.01, Folder 35)
    - Arts, General - poster, Flags: An Open Exhibition, 1970 (Box .09.01, Folder 36)
    - Arts, General - Artists' Benefit for Judson, 1975-1976 (Box .09.01, Folder 37)
    - Arts, General - proposal to revive Hall of Issues, Phyllis Yampolsky, 1976-1990 (Box .09.01, Folder 38)
    - Arts, General - GeoArts article on Peter Schulmann's Bread and Puppet Theater, After 1978 (Box .09.01, Folder 39)
    - Arts, General - Crow's Nest: An Intermedia Installation by Elaine Summers, 1979 (Box .09.01, Folder 40)
    - Arts, General - poetry - Karen (Lind-Cushen) Ethelsdattar, 1980s (Box .09.01, Folder 41)
    - Arts, General - Uranian Calendar, Uranian Press, 1982 (Box .09.01, Folder 42)
    - Arts, General - "Hansel and Gretel", 13 March 1982 (Box .09.01, Folder 43)
    - Arts, General - Artists Against U.S. Policy in Central America, 1984 (Box .09.01, Folder 44)
    - Arts, General - Political Art Documentation/Distribution, 1985 (Box .09.01, Folder 45)
    - Arts, General - Bread and Puppet Theater, Cheap Art Show, 1987 (Box .09.01, Folder 46)
    - Arts, General - Yoko Ono press kit and exhibition (not at Judson), 1989 (Box .09.01, Folder 47)
    - Arts, General - Helms Degenerate Art Show, 1989 (Box .09.01, Folder 48)
    - Arts, General - Carman Moore and the Skymusic Ensemble, 1989 (Box .09.01, Folder 49)
    - Arts, General - Jazz at Judson, flier, [1989, 1995?] (Box .09.01, Folder 50)
    - Arts, General - donation to Materials for the Arts, 1990 (Box .09.01, Folder 51)
    - Arts, General - proposals, 1990-1991 (Box .09.01, Folder 52)
    - Arts, General - Day Without Art, 1 December 1992 (Box .09.01, Folder 53)
    - Arts, General - Piano/violin recital by Nan Childress and Kara Hoffer Day, 1993 (Box .09.01, Folder 54)
    - Arts, General - Poets House, "Parallel Lines: Poetry and Dance", 1994 (Box .09.01, Folder 55)